Svitlana Khodyrieva

maygulasvetlana@gmail.com +1 502-309-1136 Louisville, KY 40220

QA Engineer Intern

Summary

Motivated ISTQB-certified tester with a strong understanding of SDLC and Agile methodologies. Possesses a solid foundation in software testing principles, bug tracking, and test case development. With six years of experience in SEO, I have developed a keen eye for detail and a strong ability to analyze requirements, identify gaps, and report bugs. Highly motivated to transition into a QA role to leverage my skills and contribute to quality assurance processes.

Skills: design and execute manual test cases to validate software functionality.

Tools and technologies: HTML/SS, MySQL, Jira, Postman, DevTools, GIT, Fiddler, Selenium IDE, XML, JSON, Source Tree, Agile, Scrum, Bugzilla, ASANA.

Management: organized and attentive to the details; ability to work independently and as part of a team; solution-focused.

Employment history

Development Coordinator, Denton Floyd (USA)

Aug 2023 - Present

- Coordinated cooperation between divisions in the pre-construction process.
- Monitored critical project dates to ensure deadlines were met.
- Maintained tracker of new and existing acquisitions.
- Assisted with data entry and research for property assessment.
- Prepared monthly reports and presentations for the Development Team.
- Maintain meeting agendas and meetings.

SEO-specialist, Individual Entrepreneur Yakimovskii (FLP) (Kyiv, Ukraine)

Jan 2017 - Jan 2023

- Developed and executed link-building and content strategies.
- Performed on-page and off-page optimization.
- Conducted technical SEO tasks: sitemap creation, robots.txt, schema markup.
- Tested websites and reported bugs.
- Monitored, tracked, and analyzed ranking performance.
- Conducted regular site audits.

Certification

- Certified Tester, Foundation Level ISTQB 23-CTFL-01482-USA, 2023
- The Fundamentals of Software Testing in QATestlab Training Center, 2023
- Software Testing Training by Mikhail Portnov, 2023
- HTML, CSS course, 2019

Education

- Master's degree specialty Manager of foreign economic activity at Eastern Ukrainian National University. 2007 – 2013

Additional Activities

- A member of the National Ukrainian Softball team, club "Nika", 2007 - 2014

<u>Languages</u>

- English - Intermediate